spundge.com 2012-09-21

# Spundge Privacy Policy — Spundge

_Last Revised August 17, 2012_

Spundge (“Spundge”, “we”, “our” or “us”) knows you care about the privacy of your personal information, and we treat it very seriously. This Privacy Policy (“Policy”) describes what information we collect and how it is used. 

## WHAT DOES THIS POLICY COVER?

This Policy applies only to information gathered during your use of Spundge.com (“Site”), which contains many links to other Web sites. The Policy does _not_ cover information collected by sites linked to from Spundge.com. 

Such external sites will have their own policies regarding the collection and use of personal information. We encourage you to learn about these other sites’ privacy and security policies before providing them with your personal information. 

## WHAT IS PERSONAL INFORMATION?

Personal information is anything that specifically identifies an individual, such as a name, address, phone number, e-mail address, and credit card or other account number. 

Personal information does not include “aggregate” information. Aggregate information is generic data we collect about how people use the Site. It helps us understand trends, patterns, and user needs so we can improve Spundge.com. In aggregate information, all individual user identities have been removed. It’s totally anonymous. 

## WHAT PERSONAL INFORMATION DOES SPUNDGE COLLECT?

There are two kinds: information you provide explicitly, and information we collect automatically through the use of cookies. 

**Information YOU provide:**

For registration, we collect only your **name** , **e-mail** , and a **password**. This information will give you full access to the Site’s services and features. 

**Automatically collected information:**

When you visit the Site, some information is automatically collected, such as your computer’s Internet Protocol (IP) address, operating system, browser type, and the time and date of your visit. This information is collected through the use of “cookies.” Cookies are small files that are stored on your computer by a Web site to give you a unique identification.

Spundge.com only uses cookies to show you relevant content, and to keep you logged in for the duration of your visit.

If you don’t want to use cookies, the “Help” button on your Web browser should direct you in disabling them. However, if you set your browser to refuse cookies, some portions of Spundge.com (and many of the sites we link to) may not function properly.

## HOW IS MY PERSONAL INFORMATION USED?

We will only use your personal information to:

  * contact you for administrative or customer service purposes
  * organize the site’s content, services, and features to better serve you during your visits

## WHO HAS ACCESS TO MY PERSONAL INFORMATION?

We do not sell or rent your personal information to anyone. Only you have access to your account, which is protected by your password.

Employees of Spundge.com do not have access to your personal information, except when absolutely necessary (e.g., to fulfill a customer service request you’ve made).

We may disclose personal information when we believe it is appropriate to:

  * comply with the law (e.g., a lawful subpoena, warrant, or court order)
  * enforce or apply our conditions of use and other agreements
  * protect the rights, property, or safety of you, Spundge.com, our employees, our users, or others

## CAN I SEE OR EDIT THE INFORMATION YOU’VE COLLECTED ABOUT ME?

You will always have access to your personal information through your account. You can make corrections, amendments, and deletions at will.

## HOW DOES THIS POLICY APPLY TO CHILDREN?

Spundge.com is not intended for use by children under the age of 13. If you are under 13 years old, you should not use, register with or otherwise provide personal information to our Site.

## WHAT ARE THE CONDITIONS OF USE?

This Privacy Policy may be modified from time to time; the date of the most recent revisions will appear at the top of this page. Your continued use of Spundge.com will constitute your acceptance of any changes or revisions made to the Privacy Policy.

Spundge Inc.  
3414 Parc Avenue, Suite 308  
Montreal, Quebec  
Canada H2X 2H5 

If you have any questions or comments about this Privacy Policy, please contact us at [privacy@spundge.com](mailto:privacy@spundge.com).
